Guide to the Alain Giami collection on sexual practices and attitudes and their health outcomes, circa 1980-2016.
Giami, Alain collection on sexual practices and attitudes and their health outcomes
- Series II. Research files, 1980-2013
  - Commentaire sur le deroulement de l'entretien, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - APEI Soissons, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Sexuality and Disability Research Material, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - CRE/INSERM Material, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Handicap, vie affective et sexualite conference, 2013-11 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Takeda Laboratories Documents, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Bayer Clinical Study, 2001-10-2001-11 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Burden of Erectile Dysfunction Analysis Plan, 2000-2002-10 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Evolution of Conception of Male Impotence, 2000-02 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Burden of Impotence Study Meeting, 2002-04 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Burden of Erectile Dysfunction Interim Results, 2002-12 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Burden of Erectile Dysfunction Interim Results Notes, 2002-12 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Patient Questionnaire - ED, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Questionnaire for Male Participants US Version, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Burden of Erectile Dysfunction Advising Meeting, 2002-04 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Burden of Erectile Dysfunction Interim Results - Female Questionnaire, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Burden of Erectile Dysfunction Interim Results, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Erectile Dysfunction Questionnaire Related Material, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Academic Articles, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Research Transparencies, Undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Academic Paper, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Quintiles Brochures, 2001-02-2002-04 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Bayer Correspondence and Notes, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - 2nd International Conference for the Social Sciences and Humanities in HIV, 2013-07-10 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Les medecins generalistes et la sexualite, 2002-09 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Recommandations aux medecins generalistes, 2005-08-31 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    Pour la prise en charge de premiere intention de la dysfunction erectile
  - Misc. Medical Publications and Articles, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Pleasure and Danger Revisited Cardiff, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - XIX Congres international des sociologues de la langue francaise, 2012-07-02 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - IASR 37th Annual Meeting Documents, 2011-08-10 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 12th Asia-Oceania Congress of Sexology, 2012-08-02 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 16th Congress of the European Society for Medicine, 2014-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - L'erotique de l'handicap, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Colloque international Biosex Pornography Class, 2009-06-05 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pornography Magazine Analysis Data, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Projet prostitution, dominatrice, erotisation du preservatif Centre OMS, 1993-05 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Presses Universitaires de France Manuscript, 2004-11-03 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pornographie chez les adolescents, 2003-06-12 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Environnements a risque, rapport fin de contrat, 2005-12 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Cerses Pornographie, 2001-01-30-2002-06-18 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Intervention de prevention aupres les jeunes CRIPS, 2001-03-21 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Articles, Magazines, News Clippings and Notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pornographic Magazines, Ads, Pamphlets, etc., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - La contribution juive a la sexologie, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Projet: l'erotisation du preservatif, 1994-03 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Enquete comportements sexuels des jeunes AMJCS, 1994-06 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Reseau Voltaire Notes d'information, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Misc. magazines and photocopies, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)